amass: v.   积聚
Lesson 59. Collecting. People tend to amass possessions. Sometimes without being aware of doing so.
第59课。收集。人们倾向于积累财产。有时不知道这样做。
Indeed they can have a delightful surprise when they find something useful which they did not know.
确实，当他们发现一些有用的东西时，他们会感到惊讶。
indiscriminate: adj. 不加选择的
They owned. Those who never have to move house become indiscriminate collectors of what can only be
他们拥有。那些永远不必搬家的人成为不可行的收藏家
clutter: n.   一堆杂物
described. As clutter, they leave unwanted objects in drawers. Coberds and addicts for years.
描述。作为混乱，它们将不需要的物体留在抽屉中。多年来，科伯德和成瘾者。
In the belief that they may one day need just those very things. As they grow old, people also
相信他们可能有一天只需要那些事情。随着年龄的增长，人们也
accumulate belongings for two other reasons. Lack of physical and mental energy. Both of which
积累物品是出于其他两个原因。缺乏身心能量。这两个
are essential in turning out and throwing away. And sentiment, things owned for a long time are
对于出来并扔掉至关重要。和情感，很长一段时间拥有的东西是
full associations with the past. Perhaps with relatives who are dead. And so they gradually acquire
与过去完全关联。也许是死了的亲戚。因此他们逐渐获得
a value beyond their true worth. Some things are collected deliberately in the home in an attempt to
超出他们真正价值的价值。有些事情是故意在家里收集的，以试图
string: n.   细线
avoid waste. Among these I would list string and brown paper. Kept by thrifty people when a
避免浪费。其中，我将列出弦乐和牛皮纸。当一个节俭的人保持
requisite: n.   必需品
parcel has been opened. To save buying these two requisites. Collecting small items can easily
包裹已经打开。保存购买这两个必需品。收集小物品很容易
mania: n.   癖好, sketch: n.   草图，图样
become a mania. I know someone who always cuts sketches out from newspapers of model clothes that
成为躁狂症。我知道有人总是从模特衣服的报纸上剪掉素描
she would like to. Buy if she had the money. As she is not rich. The chances that she will ever be
她想。如果她有钱，买。因为她不钱。她将永远存在的机会
remote: adj. （机会，可能性）少的，小的, strong-minded: adj. 意志坚强的
able to afford such purchases or remote. But she is never sufficiently strong-minded to be able to
能够负担此类购买或遥控器。但是她从来没有足够的思想
stop the practice. It is a harmless bait. But it litters up her desk to such an extent that every time
停止练习。这是一个无害的诱饵。但是它在她的桌子上徘徊在一定程度上
she opens it. Loose bits of paper fall out in every direction. Collecting as a serious hobby is
她打开了。松散的纸朝各个方向掉下来。作为一个严肃的爱好是
relaxation: n.   休息，娱乐
quite different and has many advantages. It provides relaxation for leisure hours. As just looking
完全不同，有许多优势。它为休闲时间提供放松。只是看
at one's treasures is always a joy. One does not have to go outside for amusement. Since the collection
在自己的宝藏上总是很高兴。一个人不必出去娱乐。自收藏以来
is housed at home. Whatever it consists of. Stamps. Records. First editions of books China. Glass.
被安置在家里。无论它包含什么。邮票。记录。中国书籍的第一版。玻璃。
Antique furniture. Pictures. Model cars. Stuffed birds. Toy animals. There is always something to do in
古董家具。图片。模型车。毛绒鸟。玩具动物。总有事情要做
verify: v.   查证，核实
connection with it. From finding the right place for the latest edition. To verifying facts in
与之连接。从找到最新版本的正确位置。验证事实
reference books. This hobby educates one not only in the chosen subject. But also in general matters
参考书。这种爱好不仅在所选的主题中教育一个。但总的来说
bearing: n.    关系，联系
which have some bearing on it. There are also other benefits. One wants to meet like minded collectors.
有一些方面。还有其他好处。一个人想遇到志趣相投的收藏家。
To get advice. To compare notes. To exchange articles. To show off the latest find. So one's circle
获得建议。比较笔记。交换文章。展示最新发现。所以一个人的圈子
of friends grows. Soon the hobby leads to travel. Perhaps to a meeting in another town. Possibly a
朋友的成长。很快，爱好会导致旅行。也许要在另一个城镇开会。可能是一个
specimen: n.   标本
trip abroad in search of a rare specimen. For collectors are not confined to any one country.
出国旅行以寻找一个罕见的标本。因为收藏家不仅限于任何一个国家。
Over the years. One may well become authority on one's hobby and will very probably be asked to
历年。一个人可能会成为一个人的爱好的权威，很可能会被要求
give informal. Talks to little gatherings and then. If successful. To larger audiences. In this way
给予非正式。与小聚会进行交谈。如果成功。给较大的受众。这样
self confidence grows. First from mastering a subject. Then from being able to take about it.
自信会增长。首先是掌握主题。然后从能够接受它。
constructively: adv. 有益的，积极的, contented: adj. 心满意足的, boredom: n.    烦恼，无聊
Collecting. By occupying spare time so constructively. Makes a person contented. With no time for boredom.
收集。通过如此建设性地占用业余时间。让一个人满足。没有时间无聊。